ultrahosting.com 2016-10-18

# VPS Hosting - Linux VPS Hosting | Windows VPS Hosting | VPS Web Hosting | Forex VPS Hosting | Canada Web Hosting | Reliable Web Hosting | Xen VPS Hosting | VPS Hosting | Small Business Web Hosting | Best VPS Hosting

_**ULTRAHOSTING WEBSITE PRIVACY STATEMENT**_

** ** In this privacy statement, “UltraHosting” includes all offices and subsidiary corporations of UltraHosting Inc.

UltraHosting respects the privacy of visitors to this website.  Your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by UltraHosting only in accordance with applicable privacy legislation.  Personal information is defined as information about an identifiable individual, with the exception of business contact information such as a job title or work-related telephone number, postal address, or e-mail address.

By accessing UltraHosting’s website, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of the information you provide.

This privacy statement deals only with personal information collected through UltraHosting’s website.  Any changes to this statement will be incorporated into a revised statement posted here, so that you will always have access to information on our current website information-handling practices.  To learn about UltraHosting’s information-handling practices or privacy practices beyond the Web, please email your request to [privacy@UltraHosting.com](mailto:privacy@UltraHosting.com). 

_Information Collection and Use_

If you request information, products or services, enter a contest or other promotional feature, or respond to a questionnaire or survey, you may be asked for personal information.  We value your privacy and will keep such information secure.  However at all times we reserve the right to disclose information where required by law; to comply with valid legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; to protect UltraHosting’s rights and property; or during emergencies when safety is at risk.

UltraHosting may decide to use your account information and transaction history to generate statistics and reports for internal use as well as to offer you products and services by telephone, regular mail, or email. 

If you wish, you can ask that your personal information not be used for marketing and promotional purposes.  This can be done online when you initially provide the information, or later by contacting us.

Information That Does Not Identify You

UltraHosting may share non-personal or summary information regarding our customers that does not identify you with advertisers, partners or other third parties. 

UltraHosting logs certain technical information from your computer’s web browser when you visit us on the Internet.  This information includes your Internet address, the address of the website you are coming from, the amount of time you spend visiting our website, the pages visited, the operating system and web browser software you use, and, if you link to us through a search engine, the keywords you use to find our website.  The logs do not record personal information, can be accessed only by UltraHosting, and are used solely to track visits to our site and improve its content and layout.  UltraHosting never attempts to tie this information to particular individuals visiting our website, unless that is necessary for investigating a security breach.

When you visit our website, you are assigned a temporary text file called a cookie through your web browser.  It is placed on your computer for programming purposes only and enhances your use of the site by providing a unique identifier as you move from page to page.   If you use the search engine, it remembers the keywords you enter.  The cookie is never redirected to servers outside UltraHosting.

Disclosure and Retention of Your Information

The personal information you provide through our site is never disclosed to third parties without your consent.  We do not sell or trade your personal information to other organizations or companies, and it is shared with others only in the ways explained to you at the time it is disclosed.

The account information you provide is stored in our secure databases as long as you are an UltraHosting customer.  You must contact us if you no longer want your information to be kept by us.  If you contact us with a question or comment, any information identifying you is normally kept only long enough for us to provide a response.  If circumstances require us to keep it longer than that, we will notify you.

**Accuracy of Your Information**

UltraHosting relies exclusively on you for its information about you, except for obtaining independent verification of credit card information.  To ensure that you are kept up-to-date on the products and services we offer, and that there is no interruption in our communications with you, please contact us to advise us of any changes in your information or if you wish to confirm the accuracy of the information we hold.

How Your Information Is Kept Safe during Transmission

UltraHosting strives to provide a secure online environment for the transmission of personal information such as credit card details, usernames, and passwords.  Information sent to our website is received by a secure server that encrypts the information before it is sent to us.  All data collected is protected against unauthorized access.

Contacting UltraHosting

UltraHosting accepts responsibility for the management and confidentiality of the personal information it collects through its website.  By providing this privacy statement, UltraHosting pledges its continued commitment to protecting the information you give us.  We regularly review our online information-handling practices to ensure that we are abiding by this privacy statement.  If you believe that UltraHosting is not abiding by this privacy statement or have concerns about UltraHosting's online information-handling practices, please contact us by email at [privacy@UltraHosting.com](mailto:privacy@UltraHosting.com). Your concerns will be addressed promptly. 

**_ULTRAHOSTING PRIVACY STATEMENT_**

**Your Privacy and UltraHosting**

UltraHosting is committed to upholding the confidentiality and security of personal information.  We respect the right to privacy and have instituted practices that will help ensure that personal information is handled responsibly. 

In this privacy statement, we describe how we protect the personal information of our customers, vendors and other third parties whose personal information may come under our control.  Our on-line privacy practices regarding personal information in relation to UltraHosting websites are described in our UltraHosting Website Privacy Statement.  Our commitment regarding the personal information of our employees is found in the UltraHosting Employee Privacy Statement. 

**Personal Information**

We use the term “personal information” to describe most types of information that can be linked to an identifiable individual.  Examples include an individual’s name, home address and telephone number, and social insurance number.  Information on a business card (such as job title, business address, business telephone and fax numbers, and e-mail address) is not typically considered personal information.  However, in cases where our records include both personal and business contact information and we are unable to separate them, we will handle such records as personal information.

**The Ten Privacy Principles**

UltraHosting may need to collect, use, retain, and disclose personal information to provide services to our customers and deal with vendors and other third parties.  We will request from you only the personal information necessary for bona fide business purposes, and will tell you how we intend to use this information.  Where our systems contain personal information of any third parties we will take all necessary steps to protect that information. 

To ensure that your privacy is protected, UltraHosting is committed to honouring the following ten privacy principles:

  * **Accountability  
**UltraHosting has appointed a Privacy Officer whose responsibility it is to address your privacy concerns and ensure UltraHosting’s compliance with the ten privacy principles.  Should you have concerns about how your information is handled, or any questions about our privacy policy, feel free to contact UltraHosting’s Privacy Officer by emailing [privacy@UltraHosting.com](mailto:privacy@UltraHosting.com).
  * **Identifying Purposes  
**If we intend to use or disclose personal information in ways other than those described to you at the time of collection, we will ensure that you are informed.
  * **Consent  
**UltraHosting understands that consent is required for collecting, using, or disclosing personal information (unless the law provides otherwise).  To enable you to make an informed decision about the personal information you provide, we will clearly explain to you the reasons for collecting your personal information.
  * **Limiting Collection  
**To protect your privacy, UltraHosting will only collect personal information that is relevant to the purposes you are informed of at the time of collection.  By collecting information limited to these purposes, UltraHosting helps protect you from unnecessary or accidental uses of personal information.
  * **Limiting Use, Disclosure, and Retention  
**Just as UltraHosting takes steps to limit the types of personal information we collect from you, we carefully regulate how we handle personal information.  We do not use your personal information for purposes other than those which have been consented to, or as required by law or court process (for example in a legal investigation).

Should UltraHosting require the services of third parties to handle your personal information, we will require them to adhere to privacy procedures that will keep personal information confidential.  These third parties will be given only the information necessary for performing their information-handling services.

UltraHosting does not sell or trade personal information for commercial purposes. 

UltraHosting is committed to retaining personal information on our systems only as long as is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or retained.  UltraHosting is also committed to deleting or destroying the records containing that information when they are no longer required; this will be done in ways that will ensure the continued privacy of any personal information.

  * **Accuracy  
**UltraHosting is committed to ensuring that that any records it has content control of containing personal information are accurate, complete, and up-to-date.  Although it is your responsibility to inform UltraHosting of any relevant changes in your personal information, we will take steps to ensure that if you are a provider of personal information you are able to verify the information in your file upon request.
  * **Safeguards**  
UltraHosting uses appropriate safeguards to protect the privacy of personal information.  These safeguards are designed to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification.  Your records are accessible only to staff who have been given the authority to access them and only as is necessary to provide services or otherwise deal with you.
  * **Openness**  
So that you can be confident that UltraHosting is handling personal information appropriately, UltraHosting will make information about its policies and practices concerning management of personal information readily available.
  * **Individual Access  
**If at any time you have a question about our records containing personal information, we will do our best to answer it.  You have the right to be told about the kind of personal information UltraHosting maintains for you, how it is used, and with whom it is shared.  You are entitled to challenge the factual accuracy as well as the completeness and relevance of our records.  Incorrect personal information will be promptly corrected or, if necessary, deleted.

In special circumstances, UltraHosting may need to refuse or limit an access request, for example when disclosure of the information will reveal personal information about another person or interfere with a legal investigation. 

Most inquiries about our records containing your personal information will be answered at no cost to you.  In special circumstances, however, it may be necessary to charge a fee, for example when a lot of staff time is required to gather requested information.  If a fee is necessary, you will be told in advance.

  * **Addressing Comments and Concerns  
**An important measure of UltraHosting’s compliance with the ten privacy principles is your perception of our practices and procedures.  We welcome and questions or comments about this statement and will respond to any concerns you may have about its application.  Please visit our website at [www.UltraHosting.com](http://www.ultrahosting.com/) for contact information and additional privacy information or email UltraHosting’s Privacy Officer at [privacy@UltraHosting.com](mailto:privacy@UltraHosting.com).
